Hello everyone! This is Hitomi Takamatsu of Equal Love!
Yes, so the first day of the tour ended yesterday at Fukuoka Park.
Thank you to everyone who came!
It was a lot of fun!
I'm going back to Tokyo today, but I had some time to spare, so...
So, what do you say?
I came to Boat Race Fukuoka Yama!
Yay!
Yes, we were talking about saving up parts and going to the boat race track as an expedition.
Last time, Hana-chan and I both lost.
But this time we're really too excited to come!
Thank you very much, I'm sure we'll be back today.
If you'd save up, I'm sure you'll be able to hear the voice of the staff... the first star of Japan's most extraordinary channel... the film crew.
One film crew, two managers and myself
people watching!
Oh no!
There are so few!
Let's save up everyone's energy today and go home with double the amount!
Let's definitely double it! I'll do my best!
Okay, so I'm going to make a prediction right away, but I'm going to do it again with a budget of 10,000 yen.
I'll use the money I accumulate for future parts. I'll win! I'll check it out!
One race
Oh, wait a minute. This is so hard.
Don't you see? Eyes.
I don't get it.
You're so serious.
I can't! I can't! Tears in my eyes!
We'll definitely put in a double for Hitomi.
Okay, now that I've made my mark, let's go.
So I bought the first race.
I'll definitely buy "Hitomi", so 13 and this formation.
I'm hoping the first boat will come in this formation.
But I think it'll be Abe's.
The first boat is A1, and she's from Fukuoka, so she's local.
I'm hoping he'll come.
Herabaugh and Helani are at this desk today, watching over us.
They're not answering.
Oops?
Is 5 starting outside the first?
The break-in's changed.
It's changed.
It's starting!
Let's go!
Go for it!
Feels like a start.
Whoa. Whoa?
That's cool.
Oh, wow, that's close.
Oh, my God! Four?
Go, one, one, one, one, one, one, one.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine.
Oh, no. Five is coming.
Hey, Yotchan.
Did you do it right?
Why is there a 5?
Did you cut only 5?
Yes, I only cut 5.
Here it is, here it is, here it is.
Six is coming. Six is coming.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Too good, too good, too good.
It's good. It's good.
I like it. I'll subscribe.
I'll subscribe. - I already have.
I'm getting better at turning.
I can do it! I can do it! I can do it!
Good, good, good.
But this is the most popular one, I think.
Piccoli's in danger.
Yes, sir.
It's good to be first, even if it's at the end of the line.
It's good, isn't it?
But there's a possibility of a paper cut. - Really?
I'd like to get rid of it.
But you're good at it.
You're so cool!
I knew it! The turn!
The turn!The turn.
It's like... It's like... It's like... It's like a great turn.
The first mark is important, but the turn at the second mark...
That's the highlight.
Looks scary!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Yay!
Yay! You won!
I'm so happy!
From the first race
By the way, for how much?
One, two, six, seven, eight.
Two hundred yen.
Wait a minute.
Isn't this a crazy initiative?
Fixed
And it came in as the most popular.
Right?
Yes, sir!
480 yen!
Oh, no!
I told you I wouldn't do it today.
From the first race.
But I won.
Yes, you did.
That's why we're playing.
I just got a refund for the first race.
I got 960 yen back.
But, sir, we'll see what happens to the 10,000 yen today.
So...
Let's compensate 7,500 more yen.
Race two.
Six is for A1.
It says here that he's from here.
Yummy!
Oh, man!
Auto race Fukuoka...
Fukuoka has the highest percentage of first-place finishes for the No. 3 boat in Japan.
If you buy with Hitomi, it's the best, isn't it?
But, Hitomi!
Yes!
I think she's betting on one right now.
Yes, sir.
Here's your letter.
Hmmm...
So I put in one, but I also put in one that isn't one.
I see.
When they come, let's call them "Shiro.
I'll take that one over there.
I couldn't find the reset lottery.
Ah! Yes! Listen! I'll go get one!
Sashiara-san gave me this last time and we both won, so Hana-chan and I
Hana-chan and I ate it this morning.
What? Is that why you won?
That's right! Thanks to the Reset lottery!
Thank you so much!
I don't have any daddy news today.
Oh, really?
Yes, I do.
You know my dad?
I didn't hear anything about him.
Oh, well...
I'm on my own.
So you're finally on your own?
Yes!
I bought the second race! One person
I also bought 1,2,6 box!
It's a solid race.
but I was hoping that anything could happen.
Box!
What's in Korea? How many?
Uh, one and a half dozen.
Wow!
Six!
I'm gonna need a little upgrade on the plane.
I'd like that.
He's a good guy.He's a good guy.
I want to put it up.
When I June morning comes.
It's been a while since I upgraded my plane.
Yay!
That's it.
You should definitely come.
Absolutely.
The big race is about to begin.
Oops. I can't believe we're already in the same boat again.
It changes like this?
One, two, three, four, six, five.
The sixth boat has entered the fifth course.
He's in course 5, and he's in first place.
Come on, why don't you come on?
If 3 comes in, we'll be in real trouble.
Go! It's started! Go for it!
You can do it!
Whoo-hoo!
You're too good at 6.
Yes, sir.
Hey. - Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
This is bad.
This is bad!
I knew it! Fukuoka has three!
I'm so disappointed!
All you had to do was put "3" in the box.
In this box...
This is so frustrating!
Wow!
The water was warm.
rails
me
The staff of this tasty channel sunk 3 cows!
Wow, that's amazing.
I wonder how long it will last.
I should've included this!
Oh, my God!
Rubber is so hard to make.
It's so hard!
I'll predict three races.
I don't have confidence anymore.
I've lost confidence.
Please eat some Reset gummy bears.
I've got to get my gummy bear in here.
We're going to win.
I bought the third race.
Hitomi.
And here it is this time.
Please win!
I'm in trouble.
I've got to stop him.
Here they come!
Three races.
Oh!
Go for it!
I can do it.
Here we go.
I'm scared.
No, no, no, no.
Oh?
Oh, okay.
They're here.
Come on, Ciara.
They're coming, they're coming, they're coming, they're coming, they're coming, they're coming.
They're coming. They're coming, they're coming, they're coming, they're coming.
Oh, my God, this is great.
It's the third one, and it's coming exactly the way I want it to, so far.
It's going to be okay.
I'm sure it's going to be okay.
It's the turn, it's the turn.
Let's see what you can do with the turn.
Go!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No way!Nooooooo!
That's a six.
I'm on six.
Are you in?
I'm in, I'm in, I'm in! But I'm coming in on three.
I know six better.
Six.
Six!
Oh, my God! Oh, no!
Nothing's going to happen to you.
You see, 5 is a little dangerous.
But I know that 3 is good at 3.
I know that 3 is good.
There you go.
Five, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Keep it going, keep it going, keep it going, 3 for 3, 3 for 3.
Don't let anything happen to me, don't let anything happen to me.
If you keep going like this, I'm winning.
I'm winning.
I know, I know, I know.
I'm right.
163.
I won!
What?
2,430 yen.
I won 200 yen!
Yay! Yay!
Yay!
I won, I won, I won! Oh my God, I won 200 minutes.
You won?
I won!
I did it!
I finally did it!
I've been losing a lot in my private life.
I haven't won in a long time.
I'm so happy!
Can I win with this box?
I'm not sure.
I don't know much about boat racing.
Can I win the box?
It's next on the list.
This is a chance race.
Chance races?
The most popular one has 17.
What? That's not good.
Let's win this one.
Come on, Hitomi.
Hitomi to the end.
He missed 1, 1245 on 2.
He's got the courage to miss 1. He missed 1. 2 is the better player.
I felt something. Then I'll trust you.
But Mr. Sasahara has box 1245.
I'm sure he'll win! I'm sure he'll win!
We'll get it back with this.
I'm nervous.
I'm really counting on this.
I'm going for it!
Let's go! It's okay!
You can do it! You can do it!
You'll be fine!
Wow! I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it...
Oh!
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it!
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going! You know, after this, more!
Ah! Don't give up!
Don't give up!
Suddenly!
Suddenly! You never know what's gonna happen!
Aah!
No!
One, three... no!
You don't think Hitomi will come in the last race?
Hitomi?
I'm ready to retire.
Oh, no.
Really?
Hitomi.
Hitomi?
Seriously.I'm serious.
This race is totally different.
This one, this one, and this one...
This is a big deal.
Oh, my God.
Two.
I made curry.
I'm not putting it on.
I'm telling you, it's got more body than the dancer.
Good, good, good.
Second place.
Rookie. Rookie.
No, but what do you think?
I don't know.
Oh, that's good.
One, two, three!
Is that possible? Finally.
It's so simple.
Simple one, two, three.
I want it to be simple.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
A-ha-ha
Uh-oh.
How about another money?
I spent all 10,000 yen.
I lost about 4,000 yen.
What? You really lost?
I lost!
But you know what? Isn't he growing?
Certainly, I'm growing.
I went to Boat Race Fukuoka from race 1 to race 4 with 10,000 yen again.
I have 6,320 yen in my pocket now!
I have money! I have money in my hand!
This alone is a huge growth.
Minus 3,680 yen.
I lost 3680 yen today.
I lost, but I still have 6,302 yen in my pocket.
I think I'm one of the lucky ones.
Sashiara-san!
Yes, sir!
How did it go?
I'm going to eat bean sprouts for a while.
I'm going to eat some bean sprouts.
No! Sprouts!
We've lost more than anyone else in the Boca Raton Race Club so far.
One by one.
Is that what happened?
We're losing, and we're losing even more.
Oh no!
Let's all buy in economy today.
Economy!
So, that was the 3rd Boat Racing Club!
May there be a fourth one. Thank you very much. Bye-bye.